nowvisitor.com 2016-07-27

# Now Visitor - 隐私权

## 隐私权

I. **Introduction**  
Now Visitor (“Company”, “Nowvisitor”, or “We”) understand that your privacy is very important to you and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.   
You can be assured that your personal information will only be used in accordance with this policy.  
Nowvisitor may change this policy from time to time by updating this page without any notice. You should check this page regularly to ensure that you are up to date with the latest privacy policy. The date of which the policy was last modified will be listed at the top of the page for your reference.  
II. Children Under the Age of 13  
Our Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Anyone under 13 may not provide any personal information on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal data from minors. If you are under the age of 13, please avoid using the Site and do not provide any information to the Site.  
III. Information We Collect About You  
Our website collects information about our Users. We may collect the following types of information:  
1\. Information You Provide  
We collect information by which you may be personally identified such as full name, email address and country. This information is collected directly from you when you provide it to us when signing up for an account or changing your account settings.  
2\. Cookies, IP Addresses and Log Information  
As you interact with and use the Site, Service or application, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns including traffic data, location data, details about your visit and site usage logs. We may also collect information about your computer or device, internet connection, IP address, operating system and browser type.  
The technology we use to automatically collect your data and keep you logged in may include cookies, flash cookies or web beacons. In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior.  
For example, we may use Google’s “remarketing” service to target our ads to you based on your prior use of the Site when you visit on other sites in Google’s content network.  
IV. How We Use Your Information  
We use the information we collect from you or that you provided to us:  
• To present User Websites to you and other Users based on location  
• To determine your geolocation by country code  
• To provide you with information or content tailored to you  
• To inform you about our blog posts, updates, latest offers and newsletters  
• To alert you of Site or Service changes  
• To notify you about your account or subscription  
• To make website analysis for web marketing and service improvements  
• To provide you with customer service via support ticket system  
• In the event of payment disputes.  
• For any other purpose with your consent  
We will never sell your personal information to third parties.  
V. Disclosure of Your Information  
We may collect and disclose anonymous and aggregated information of Users without restriction for the purpose of product research, improvement of Service and other commercial purposes.  
We may also disclose your personal information to comply with any court order, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.  
VI. Updating Your Information  
You can update any of your personal information including your password by logging into the Site and visiting the settings page. If you would like to remove your personal information from the Site or close your account, please contact us at contact@nowvisitor.com.  
VII. Linking Your Gravatar  
You agree to give permission to Now Visitor to use your gravatar on the website and to display the image as your account’s avatar for the Site. VIII. Security Disclaimer  
We have implemented several security measures to protect your personal information from becoming loss or stolen from unauthorized Users. All information you provide to us is stored in a database within a state-of-the-art data center park.We do not store any payment login information such as your PayPal or Payza username/passwords however we do collect transaction ids of your purchases on the Site.Payment non Refundable. The security of your data also depends on you. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. It is also recommended to not use the same password you have used on other websites. We will never ask for your password so be careful about giving this information out in public areas like message boards.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your data on the Site as it may be vulnerable to hackers or hardware failure. Although we do backup our database regularly, any transmission of personal data is at your own risk. Nowvisitor will not be responsible for any damages done.  
If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please e-mail contact@Nowvisitor.com
